<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<thrive>
    <data noupdate="1">
        <record id="case_matter_close_mail_template" model="mail.template">
            <field name="name">Case Matter Close Mail Template</field>
            <field name="model_id" ref="tk_law_management.model_case_matter"/>
            <field name="subject">Closure of Law Case Matter</field>
            <field name="email_from">{{object.company_id.email}}</field>
            <field name="partner_to">{{ object.customer_id.id }}</field>
            <field name="body_html" type="html">
                <table style="width: 100%">
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            Dear Customer,
                            <br/>
                            <h4>
                                <strong>
                                    <t t-out="object.customer_id.name"/>
                                </strong>
                            </h4>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                </table>
                <p>
                    We hope this email finds you well. We are writing to inform you that the law case matter you were
                    involved in has been officially closed.
                </p>
                <p>
                    After careful examination of all relevant information and legal proceedings, we are pleased to
                    inform you that the case has reached its conclusion. The legal team has successfully resolved the
                    <strong>
                        <t t-out="object.case_matter"/>
                    </strong>
                    , and we wanted to provide you with this update.
                </p>
                <hr/>
                <table>
                    <tr>
                        <td colspan="2">
                            <strong>
                                Here are the key details regarding the closure of the law case matter
                            </strong>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <strong>
                                Case Matter:
                            </strong>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <t t-out="object.case_matter"/>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <strong>
                                Case Open Date:
                            </strong>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <t t-out="object.open_date"/>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <strong>
                                Case Closure Date:
                            </strong>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <t t-out="object.close_date"/>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <strong>
                                Case Status:
                            </strong>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            Closed
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                </table>
                <hr/>
                <p>
                    We understand that legal matters can be stressful and time-consuming, and we want to express our
                    gratitude for your patience throughout this process. We appreciate your cooperation and trust in
                    our legal team.
                </p>
                <p>
                    If you have any questions or concerns regarding the closure of the case or if you require any
                    additional information, please feel free to contact our customer support team at
                    <strong>
                        <t t-out="object.company_id.phone"/>
                    </strong>
                    or reply to this email. Our team is here to address any inquiries you may have.
                </p>
                <p>
                    We would like to take this opportunity to thank you for choosing our services and placing your trust
                    in our legal expertise. Your satisfaction is of utmost importance to us, and we are glad that we
                    were able to bring this matter to a successful conclusion.
                </p>
                <p>
                    Once again, we sincerely appreciate your cooperation and understanding throughout this process. If
                    there is anything else we can assist you with in the future, please do not hesitate to reach out to
                    us.
                </p>
                <p>
                    Thank you for your attention, and we wish you the best in all your future endeavors.
                </p>
                <h6>
                    Best regards,
                </h6>
                <h5>
                    <strong>
                        <t t-out="object.company_id.name"/>
                    </strong>
                </h5>
                <hr/>
                <span>
                    <h6>
                        <t t-out="object.company_id.name"/>
                    </h6>
                    <t t-out="object.company_id.phone"/>
                    <br/>
                    <t t-out="object.company_id.email"/>
                    <br/>
                    <t t-out="object.company_id.website"/>
                </span>
            </field>
            <field name="auto_delete" eval="True"/>
        </record>
    </data>
</thrive>